[{
  "question": "What is the translation: System.out.println(\"BlitzCode rules!\");",
  "answer": "print(\"BlitzCode rules!\")",
  "wrongAnswers": ["console.log(\"BlitzCode rules!\");", "println(\"BlitzCode rules!\")", "System.out.print(\"BlitzCode rules!\")"]
},
{
  "question": "What is the translation: System.out.println(\"Hello, World!\");",
  "answer": "print(\"Hello, World!\")",
  "wrongAnswers": ["console.log(\"Hello, World!\");", "println(\"Hello, World!\")", "System.out.print(\"Hello, World!\")"]
},
{
  "question": "What is the translation: System.out.printf(\"The value of x is %d\", x);",
  "answer": "print(\"The value of x is\", x)",
  "wrongAnswers": ["System.out.printf(\"The value of x is %d\", x)", "println(\"The value of x is\", x)", "printf(\"The value of x is %d\", x);"]
},
{
  "question": "What is the translation: System.out.print(5);",
  "answer": "print(5)",
  "wrongAnswers": ["System.out.print(5)", "console.log(5);", "printf(5);"]
},
{
  "question": "What is the translation: System.out.println(\"10 + 5 = \" + (10 + 5));",
  "answer": "print(\"10 + 5 =\", 10 + 5)",
  "wrongAnswers": ["System.out.println(\"10 + 5 = \" + (10 + 5))", "console.log(\"10 + 5 = \" + (10 + 5))", "print.MATH(\"10 + 5 =\" + (10 + 5));"]
},
{
  "question": "What is the translation: System.out.printf(\"The value of pi is %.2f\", Math.PI);",
  "answer": "print(\"The value of pi is\", format(math.pi, '.2f'))",
  "wrongAnswers": ["System.out.printf(\"The value of pi is %.2f\", Math.PI)", "print(\"The value of pi is\", format(Math.PI, '.2f'))", "console.log(\"The value of pi is\", Math.PI);"]
},
{
  "question": "What is the translation: System.out.printf(\"%s is %d years old\", name, age);",
  "answer": "print(\"%s is %d years old\" % (name, age))",
  "wrongAnswers": ["System.out.printf(\"%s is %d years old\", name, age)", "console.log(\"%s is %d years old\", name, age);", "print(\"%s is %d years old\" % name, age)"]
},
{
  "question": "What is the translation: System.out.print(\"\\n\");",
  "answer": "print()",
  "wrongAnswers": ["System.out.print(\"\\n\")", "console.log();", "print(\"\")"]
},
{
  "question": "What is the translation: System.out.println(x == y);",
  "answer": "print(x == y)",
  "wrongAnswers": ["System.out.println(x == y)", "console.log(x == y);", "print(x, \"==\", y)"]
},
{
  "question": "What is the translation: System.out.println(\"The result is: \" + result);",
  "answer": "print(\"The result is:\", result)",
  "wrongAnswers": ["System.out.println(\"The result is: \" + result)", "console.log(\"The result is: \" + result)", "print(\"The result is:\")"]
}]